In the.
In. The OR.
The. Out of the shadows of the
past as from a faded tapestry of time as
procession slow and past I stepped into
a bear with me
a while you are and see I engage to
look upon another age and age when I'm
a human tied up to Midway machinery road
to experiment with the wider punishment my
D.C. Wants never shown a bright
happy hour and in as high
a romantic hour so come with
me to find some old to fire
a days when heartbeat high on blood was
young and hate was bold and hard cross
father daughter died for love in our glory
and then and friendship reached its peak
with men friends were friends
in those brave days.
I gave Doris for the mystic phrase.
And our lives for the mystic. Columns
during our own are really called
love for one and one for our.
Code.
On the day of September and the year of
Our Lord sixteen hundred thirty eight. I
think excitement runs. Are going to
enjoy a general holiday in patients in
a way I mean America. And.
Its majesty Louis the thirteenth King up
front. Maintaining his royal authority
to the wishes of others is him so we can
change and lives in the only smiles of
a small circle of say. The
court is alive with intrigue
parties within the parties conspiracies
beyond conspiracies plots and counterplots
.
Eminence must endure the cardinal two story
she. Is the greatest statesman of the
day and manipulates the strings which guide
the king. Is the real power struggles
coming and often roof. Still no one questions
his devotion to the glorious kingdom
of.
On this most precious
morning the King pays
a state visit. TO is clear. It is the custom
for the sovereign and his courtiers to
attend the expectant royal mother than
to lose child is born. Early little
valley. Girl and. The
Kenyan of the king's Musketeers. Relieved
of his duties in court for the day he
hurried to the home of his sweetheart
Constance bonnet. Constance it seems to the
queen and is expected at the
palace so she can't carry law.
And. The minute the even
the most eager lover
by error can sometimes just
a Miss or Mrs kiss. And
. The king's carriage. Arrives for const.
She carries an infant play in the closure
of the basket for the queen. In.
One.
Morning. When the railroad.
The OR.
A kiss truly is
a delicate plant for acquiring privacy to
grow and with in the blood and dreams of
our loved. Little. World.
As.
And. And.
The and.
Rather the belle of the Cathedral of Notre
Dame remind our canyon of his friend and
fellow Musketeer out him
if he might be in danger.
Alice had threatened to continuously
attentions with the pretty owner of
a roving provocative I one fortunately is
married to an officer in the cardinal's
God. Gods naturally resent these
attentions from this Musketeer I dismissed
straight. As not the cardinal from.
Litanies duels with the king's Musketeers.
While our. Supply of the musketeers instant
help comes from the most fearsome the
steel in the King. George prophet
railed on Kings musketeer
and Musketeer as gentle efforts to get
a deadly Swordsman is able to kill
with his left hand is with the right.
Not to hang up. The palace from
a. Cardinal God this is no private
fight and Musketeers against the
Cardinals God is starting to fall apart
and I'm with both on one of the odds one
two three four five six ten down to four
five to turn to have to wonder Two simple
draw us Q On a draft
card let's measure half
a point. On God's. Knowledge
or a challenge to our wager
to steal but just to get
a lot of the cardinals killed
in a friendly fight with
a marketeer until. Such
as always is the state he has capacity
content in that is quicker I had him
a bundle drinking sort.
Of us can put out
a hand and pick up the top three players
for why waste energy working. On driver
and come inside with.
The old driver swears we're going to damage
his master was getting his horses loose
he has
a terrible life he has trouble everybody
is mean to him here. I mean to. Come
out now take your temper out
on me girlfriend. Now feel
better now we can talk how when you're the
price of your house and more on God when
I challenge you to games
this is not for the new.
Dice
a kind. Is done in times of crisis. Is
like riding high now and then returns to
the dice game and I think I'm playing
a while longer he wins hands down from the
I've had it God while waiting for the
late inning on the cusp. Of
those two as women on his mind.
In the start the only battle the Musketeers
ever lost and fair fight of course it
has to be with.
The first time in his life
a panic stricken plus
a stranger terrified by
not about him. And I miss
Springs bravely to the side of his
comrades be together. But that Kenyon
hears only the pounding of the lovers.
Before the battle at last week's post when
he leaps to meet the pope. And draw is.
The sight. You know he was here in the
discretion of the better part of valor of
the British the devil's in the
deep blue sea. A tourist the last.
One.
Makes more than the city of and. Russia
may on the gates of the great the people
are admitted to the court.
Adjoining the Green's apartment
Constance prepares to lay at. War.
She is informed by Father Joseph the
cardinal's trust an engine of the imminence of
the royal bed.
Lola.
Oh the good. Lord.
And celebrate his blunder from
one day to become Linda forty.
I can custom his royal father
present him to the people of the
RAF
. But in the Queen's
bedroom another cry of it
one of those gray haired tens of destiny
and Constance is the first one the tired
dozing midwife.
The OR.
Rather Joseph's craft about the consequences
of this extraordinary event this news
must be conveyed discreetly to Cardinal
Richelieu before it gets abroad he writes
a message inside the Methodist medicine
and that for the cardinal's eyes alone.
There are metal. And your eminence.
To do the spoken I think had of the most
powerful faction in court working always
in self-interest against the king and
Cardinal protecting loyalty to both.
The. Old. And
the set the day of
a caution on the part of Father Joseph as
indeed well founded goes for having many
times the messages are taken to his eminence
becomes inquisitive The result is by
a simple trick to learn the
secret past the cardinal.
Substitution of scraps of paper.
Cardinal realizes that enemies of the regime
can do irreparable damage to and try.
To live on part is appointed
on Crown smart and.
Helpless tone between two factions.
Including the twins must indeed be for
ever God If France prestige. And if he
the cartoonist to retain its power.
No pretended this. A true prince the
rush for seize an opportunity father
Joseph is instructed to prepare for
a long voyage. All
. The cardinal has
a plan is and the taste of.
Amanda Roche. And then.
An.
Awareness constant travel
position of a bicycle once I was
a could it might well spell the
future of France cardinal tried as
a keeper lips sealed. Rather.
And the war. Will.
Restore you interest the wily droshky
always comes to suspect she must not be
committed to see anyone until further notice
the cardinal is not at liberty to tell
its reasons the garage floor is making
its own flag of the of the world.
And then. Accordance with the card of
Commander father Joseph accompanied by the
midwife secretly takes the twin away to
the Spanish border and child shall be
raised as
a common it was no knowledge
of Israel but at. The
doorway while in the great ballroom the
king of the reception are dispersed by. And
in on
a cradle should have killed two sons he
might have been less self-satisfied than
the cardinal's congratulation.
To the notorious Melissa winter duros for
comes to reveal this chance to fight the
future of France maybe in their hand he
tells her he will turn Constance over to
her she is to escort Constance
to consider sending
a male air force her to tell the whole of
the cardinal secret and plan he will play
with. One against the other cardinal
against King for his own ambitions.
And then earlier in. The event.
Or or.
Even And then.
They're going constantly. One of the
chair carriers runs with the news to the
Musketeers barracks. The.
Sunshine and wake up Constance
taken by force I don't watch from.
The the. Top I'm
a stop loss rescue. For one
and one for all and hang the tag.
A while if she does and no motocross still
with this angry guest comment on just.
For stuck up powerless to help.
Just.
As.
Rochelle want to stop it he will not talk.
Goes on Larry please come or fall
two hundred feet. Are going to die.
It. Cardinals God look great when.
Strength. To. Strength.
Our only one. Armed Response
bank account understand.
To the rest your. Take on
granted already and the cardinal tells
of the risk of trickery in capturing of
Constance's abduction by my lady. Went.
To. The original You're never going to reach
the will to confront the deal or are.
Accused exposed and nearness to drag
on and he confessed that he is and
deeply like. An eminent
breaks the rules for skipping
a member's authority entitled banished
from both Court and country forever.
Caring for the safety of consonance
the cardinal species and the children
illegitimate and. Before
dawn the next morning
a convent of and get
married. To Lulu moon.
When. Later when her show
is the unsuspecting and
a prisoner is an enemy of the state to
be confined to the convent on what is
a card.
Of banished devotion or smarting under his
militia and lingers and our. Listeners
lost eases the last of his wealth and
a desperate gamble and buys
the services of rough and.
Sure the car. Next find our
tennis Three Musketeer friends
and put them to the salon.
The. COMMERCIAL FOR still dreams of himself
and terms of the most powerful man.
After hours of. If I'm
elated to win testicular.
And then.
I need interested in scrupulous my lady
to want to speak to the children come to
telling all.
Of the or.
No Constance punished is not. The Here's
a boy. I
love. For all of the awful
one.
In politics.
Mark and the public. Burned by
a branding iron and with
flesh find walls. Close
to Constance is
a criminal My lady twenty three desperate.
Cost US Mexican active crime by the laws
of France the lady must face
public execution. Of that.
Life or that.
The OR.
Canyon is Constance with but
a club loves him above all. And
then she managed three where.
The other was.
Ten and strains to hear the faint
pulse of her words. Constance died.
The Musketeers technology to winter to
a punishment. Is
imminent the consciousness
traveled through the night.
He hears
a good clue from the mother.
Comes to escape. Its
. Fake smiles. And.
A M.
M N. Arrest the
murderous my lady to winter and
all in contact with her I am.
A free marketeers are full of promise and
ice and rain just take the law into their
own hands and deliver the murderous
to the public execution. Order.
And of course cut throats
close enough my God Mr.
Wrenn.
I am. An.
Some distance away the marketeers
a captured but at deadliest rivals the
cardinals God formally arrest Musketeers for
continuing to keep the
light on and. Disarm the
Musketeers are set against
the wall for execution. And.
Your God to protect the lives of my friend
in the land and they shall ever then.
Know lasts
a moment under. Constant. And
murderous executed. Enough
blood and shed now the strife ticks
musketeer and God shall end.
It. Start and please take
this friend of theirs to be
a harsh penalty. Racial use plan concerns
the state and these continuing disputes
between his god McCain's musketeer. The
four musketeers must never to come together
again on pain of death.
Judgement. All right in. The
Musketeers are banished each to his own
problems never do this at Paris again or
set foot beyond the
bounds of his own feet.
As for you Dartanion. A splendid soldier
a liar to boast to. You will henceforth
show the bodyguard of the future king
beloved of France the nations one.
One fell swoop as strife done.
The Musketeers prepare for their
banished. And. Godspeed to well.
Eternal friendship shall
not. All for one. One
for all. The
world in. The.
Five years have passed. France at
the. End from Prince close to buoyant
Cardinal Richelieu driven on by the
responsibilities of high office lives and I may
retire. And our own father
educate his son and cordially.
And failing else his eminence live in
hourly expectation of death coupled by with
a second twenty million
identical likeness to the air.
Holes. In the old.
Dangers inherent are obvious and weigh
heavily on the cardinal's mind it aside they
must protect depends on how it eminence
provides that the right for twenty may
always be identified on the other for the
aid of the club jewelery is called the
gold the bloom to be broken
the smaller piece hangs on
a chain around the throat of the infant
Prince. And it may to be places about the
neck of Captain D'Artagnan.
And so by joining the Peace is the true
heir to the throne of France and the
princes first Guardian are known to one
another for all time is time to say.
I hold
a secret. And two hands upon
me my. Life ring and. And
the great price either.
A great statesman passes
into history. A church loses
a noble servant and the ship
of state is without its pilot.
I plan to speak with the British and you
and Constance head. Of that was. Told.
The story. About the Spanish one of the
princes twin brothers we had by servants of
the late Cardinal banished to Russia for
living there by old the twenty one there
is no the I by this time he has only
to wait patiently for the proper day.
Of the Swiss. Upon
the death of Louis the thirteenth year to
the throne of the dolphins he was called
the game hunters King Louis the Fourteenth
both and the twin had known the man and
the brothers are alike as two peas in
a pod. Twenty
years have passed and bought and
for your betters iron willed
a breakup was that hello.
Herman. I will ride one spot
was formerly the clarion
call all the ones anyone or.
During the years to root for the conniving
cannot be exiled twin under his control
secretly they have returned our. Rosa
Flores lavished upon the usurper the
trappings of royalty teaching him to copy
even the handwriting of his brother the
king. In the quality of the Spirit
so generous in a king is replaced in
a brother by hatred and this is.
The king Eleanor for snipings long awaited
news within the week no doubt and after
a lifetime of loyalty this will retire and
leave the court young king of the word
out about it. Every
detail of the planet on
a. Map entries to overpower he
could approach the royal apartment
signoff. In. Turn
order in. Or
or.
Insist
a week to watch for tells apart and you
will be his Majesty Louis the Fourteenth
King of France. The fourteenth King
of France in the time and last day
in the sun and yet the king is applied
himself to an education and horsemanship
sportsmanship and swordsmanship. No two
men were ever closer except they were
father and son. Were already.
In it.
Culch. I was early on and entered the world
that lived in the King and by tonight
he feels happiest ever to turn his King A
secure the state are safe but I've come
on bring the nation the coins are matched
on this final night of partying.
And the world happy memories of
a delightful evening with Captain
Dartanion arrives outside his lodging in
a minute to find himself attempt by rough
Anguilla to get commented at fifty deals
with an egg and examine it on The Late
Show the men came to the edge of an open
sewer by their own capability
called Body and fire on.
One of the.
Fire. And I believe those.
For. A scrub full Dartanion
returned to his lodging for
a peaceful man to be waylaid on
a city street or something new. He had
spent the evening with this case.
Perfect. Analysis and I'm fighting to.
Angeles where not when I should have been.
Socially hard as this term
for the safety of this king.
Only. For.
Old Rule or most always
plan is working without
a hitch and trees at the outer gate have
been overpowered entry is forced into the
inner quadrangle a palace and head to
a seventh post and leading to long
forgotten cellars. Expects I was found
nowhere I had no warning.
For the. Potential waves impatiently below
for the deed which will make him king.
In the end
a room to the king and tempered arose for
his maggot awaits his master's signal
ready for the final crash or even.
A little after eleven o'clock on this fateful
night in one tragic moment rats lose
their rightful king.
Well good I'm certain
a few things are not king Louis the
Fourteenth surrounded by strangers looks
unbelievingly at
a venomously married
likeness of him. Watches
his royal brother with
a lifetime of hate air. Arose from his
plans and cleverly text and double
checked he names told the
true king a prisoner is
a threat to the head of the separation
to rebel against his commanders.
At drugstores or to his cohorts took the
king of his night attire and in exchange
dress him in the Ustep and
close. All the holes.
Into the palace tellers the messenger reports
Presley can escape his body thrown in
the river. Complete
clients have a job. For
a. While.
For an iron mask invention
of the devil an iron mask
a prison within a prison is placed over
the head of the rightful king though with
a forty locked at the neck his
countenance concealed all the.
Trooping away.
In the choir the royal apartments the
true kings that is occupied by the will
separate trust and services have been
spirited away the twins' lackeys have
replaced. Arose from his
plan is completely.
Ruled by you driven yet a lunatic by
a solitary childhood by the rush towards
life by his own place and dreams truly
a man.
Suffering in human life is
proportioned to human strength. And
a young king stupefied him crushed
found himself led a prisoner to
a cell in the shadows and Marguerite in
the south of France he founded first the
death like sleep then has its
remains he believed himself to be
a spectator of album both the phantom of
his own suffering the torture the more
terrible since it might be ten
not. Ten on death. How can I have
died. I am a king yet not
a king and thrown upon
a few nearly all college now no Again
God Do not punish me or done nothing
by my last punished. By God close the
children of the dungeon fall upon his
shoulders. Hold twelve the real Louis the
Fourteenth in the living held to remain
thus the rest of his days.
The queen mother. Always restrict prevented
from seeing his son determines finally
to pay him
a visit. Off in place
to lay a faction at incredibly low in
a fourteen two hour she
finds it repulsed. Again
doubts. What change
melody might. Do things
again of the other. The or the rush for
her is the king's apartment fearful that
a mother's heart is and the truth. And
pretense of humility he asked the queen
mother at least. Their take.
All right.
Rochelle is determined. Shall not
happen again and whispers debt.
Levels day by day night upon night the
prisoner pays to some way to get word
to Doc and. I haven't found
Fishman hopes to get.
It finished scratching a message to Q.
And As all good players must
be disparaged answered.
Milligan macro ironic and then I
catch apparently from heaven.
Fisherman read the name of D'Artagnan
the idol of the nation the written word
beloved name and. In message
here I did not know what.
Paris goes about its daily affairs unaware
that its rightful king languishes in
prison and the queen mother
has still faces death as
a humble fisherman hastens to the telly
and help. The tiny and stayed on in Paris
and with head and eyes and continually
find themselves barred from the court. Day
by day week by week audience with the king
has been released. For him and Curtis
weird new. Story hardly the only
cast list on time Innotek upon as.
An iron mask minus the.
Image. Etching of Aquinas his
own act. Fool.
Fool. Come friend eat and drink
there is business and last for me at.
Training is way through the perfume
through to the court scattering idlers
Dartanion finds himself a stranger in
a strange atmosphere and there is reason
to think for this curious tension to rush
for and the king. Cannot be the boy I
help nurture into manhood This is not the
face of Mikey. It was not
his hands at risk not
a parrot still not engaged the point.
What's been happening at court Carlos was
back in favor of disgraced exile once more
sporting about the throne room and the
king's presence at tennis
amazed and shocked. That
further shocked us and start
a chain and coyness past the rush for he
can believe his eyes and all ears he said
the king may never left his
royal person. You know he has
a touch of conversation the other one.
And suddenly hears the dying voice of
Constance. One. Hundred one.
What did she mean. A message
signed by the royal coin.
KING Not a king and a quarter lie
with known faces Dartanion smells
a rat
a rabbit seen him and his MORNING.
Telephone does the relatives. Calling it
by.
More or All right.
All right little do they reckon
with the resourceful old must.
Not and in order the king's loyal group
to be hurried to meet him at the shadows
and Marguerite. Areas that we dispatch to
his old friends the Three Musketeers I
saw spot and I missed it was my
pears Dante had need of you.
One for All and all for what.
The King is up to and lives
and knows this too is
a place. At the even now is
reached the prison gate.
A restaurant cannot believe
his future lies in
a common place. Quickly
resolved to end all doubts. He decided to
write at the end of his trip to prevent
any attempt to free the king.
Of the darkness which the
shadows and muttering in
a comet will join. In on
the cover of the raging
storm he rose to the rest of the cast many
a time of the another day and the cold is
caught up at. Eleven No they are beyond
that the armory in the main hall and
staircase to the tower itself. Up there is
a man in the eye and
ask the writer in the.
Listener's mundane can find the
entrance to the US knowledge.
Of the.
Field was as prepared as it alone.
The man returned to the other bank to
await the arrival of help. In the.
Us a few years older
a little more brittle the same brave companion
as I'm all ready and willing for any
camp.
Lejeune in our area missed.
In
a manner. That's
. Now two of the million
comments arrived I was trying to
wait for Oprah for us no
time for explanations as
a job to be done forward. To
the racks of gunpowder barrels to the
main arc and the tower staircase itself.
You're in. The country.
Where the prison at Guantanamo
Bay Cuba six seven. Eight.
The last time you know device this is
true and right something new in the
fourteenth King of France.
And Russia and our.
Calendars met. Last night and
here's why again and again
in the. World.
When.
Things.
And.
Best. Friend Margaret not
a carpenter any as much as I do miss
companion cholesterol blood. The.
Last. Minute.
With.
The. Lens and the.
Rest.
All for one and. The start and cherished
friends that I should always.
Want good times we had together.
Good profit was there where. You died
as you live. For love of country
in the service of your King. A fisherman
gives warning of the approach of
enemies. And.
When.
One.
Of the Marketeers around it
came galloping up to Paris. For
a ride hard in the last effort to
keep his house from something.
Under ten to one.
Can imagine and. On about it.
Oh well Gallant I missed creatures Alex
structure down meanwhile as part of the
stories with the rose for
a. Lot
of the highest price of all
our past joined his comic.
The of. And without knowing
his own peril have wit have
can entertain his royal
mother Alice lunch.
Room cunningly is as
a private matter. When
war. When.
On come from the palace
friends of. Friends
start and in brief relief can make
a safe. Haven to cater. To
. To. The queen mother
suspects this attempt on
a life. Which is
brutal
a subtle poison already responsible for
many an agonizing death raise your glass
Madame drink to your came
to your country and it's
a lustrous people. Come to
France. Tears you refuse
it is easy to confess on the can.
Tell just what I want to cry.
The.
Usurper finally get his rightful crown to
run for its own damn the bill invention
the Iron Mask. Is the end of his days.
With. Us. World
her. Start and End for the
way the poisoned wine with
separate kicks with it around
then and. Then. When the world.
War World War One.
Dartanion knows himself mortally wounded
allows no signs of my that this is.
One.
Of the. Blood the weapon of the metric
crimson evidence on the blade for.
One. Grateful
oil look for Captain Dartanion
to honor him with the baton of
a Marshal of France. But
where is the market.
For. In. A quandary sounds when it came
to commands and his cry to find
his friend and mentor. What
a man may think when he knows that the
approach of death is six. Between himself
and his make. Apps
a gallant Musketeer thinks most of us
must love Constance. And all the tender
lonely years kept warm by her memory. He
dies in the hope of faith that she might
welcoming. That once again they might be
one. How can they die these bright ones
how many such energy once released imprisoned
by her tone or grace. We die as we
lived say they were life. And
what life how can there be death.
Only remember only open a little
more lawless they want to ride
a fine horse or to prop up blade or carouse
on them our lawn only want to come one
come all.
And so passed
a brave and glorious man in on our.
Own list think and we live again
we live forever now with us now is
that it's one for all and all for one.
Another one is in front of the most
inspiring days when Hearts get high I love.
Them all installed in the past is gone to
No one died I love anonymous glory and
then my life was life and when I met.
or
Or
.